好
Okay...
X-10(先进网络技术)已经联网了
The x-tens are online.
先生们  我现在要通过这台电脑发射一个信号
Gentlemen, I am now about send a signal
连接到我们当地的互联网服务供应商
From this laptop through our local isp
以光速在光纤电缆中传输到旧金山
Racing down fiber-optic cable at the speed of light
再通过地球同步轨道卫星
To san francisco, bouncing off a satellite
反射到葡萄牙的里斯本
In geosynchronous orbit to lisbon, portugal,
在那里数据将
Where the data packets
切换到跨大西洋海底电缆
Will be handed off to submerged trans-atlantic cables
最终汇聚到加拿大新斯科舍省的哈里法克斯
Terminating in halifax, nova scotia
再通过微波中继跨越整个大陆
And transferred across the continent
最后回到我们的互联网服务供应商
Via microwave relays back to our isp
而X-10的接收器就连接着这个...
And the x-ten receiver attached to this...
灯
Lamp.
快看  快看  我鸡皮疙瘩都起来了
Look at me. look at me. I've got goose bumps.
我们试试音响  准备好了没
Are we ready on the stereo?
快试试音响
Go for stereo.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
-你好  -你好
Hi. hello. hello.
声音有点大
It's a little loud.
没问题  马上关小它
No problem-- turning it down.
旧金山  里斯本  哈里法克斯
San francisco, lisbon, halifax...
瞧  好了吧(法语)
And voila.
好  谢了
Okay, thanks.
等等  等等  你是不是没明白我们在干什么
Hang on, hang on. do you not realize what we just did?
明白  你们用电脑把音响关小了
Yeah, you turned your stereo down with you laptop.
不是  我们通过互联网走了地球一圈
No, we turned our stereo down by sending a snall
发送了一个命令把音响关小的
Around the world via the internet.
其实这样一个遥控装置
You know, you can just get one of those universal remotes
在瑞帝优上(美国电子产品零售企业)里有买  而且很便宜
At radio shack. they're really cheap.
不  不  你还是没明白
No, no. You don't get it.
霍华德  开启公共接入功能
Howard, enable public access.
公共接入已开启
Public access enabled.
真不赖  伙计们  我先走了
Boy, that's terrific. I'll see ya.
别  等等  等等
No, hang on, hang on.
看到没?
See?
没有
No.
在中国四川省的某个人
Someone in szechwan province, china
正在通过他的电脑
is using his computer
远程开关我们的灯
To turn our lights on and off.
那倒是很方便
Well, that's handy.
我提个问题  为什么要做这个?
Here is the question. Why?
因为我们可以做到
Because we can.
他们发现了远程遥控汽车
They found the remote-control cars.
等等  等等  车顶上是什么?
Well, wait, wait, what's on top of that?
无线网络摄像头  打个招呼
Wireless web cams. wave hello.
那辆大货车来自德克萨斯州的奥斯丁
The monster truck is out of austin, texas,
而"蓝毒蛇"正在被一个来自
And the blue viper is being operated
以色列特拉维夫郊区的人控制
From suburban tel aviv.
你也许应该穿条裤子
You may want to put on slacks.
什么
What?
快停下来
Ew, stop it.
不  离我远点
No leave me alone
那个红色雪佛兰是谁控制的?
Who's running the red corvette?
是我
That would be me.
天才也性感  第一季  第九集
The Big Bang Theory S01 E09
你们知道吗  在将来
You know, in the future
当我们能把大脑取出来放到罐子里时
When we're disembodied brains in jars,
我们回过头看看这八小时  会觉得那真无聊
We're going to look back at this as eight hours well wasted.
我不想被放到罐子里
I don't want to be in a jar.
我想把我的大脑放在机器人身上
I want my brain in an android body.
最好身高八英尺  身材健美
Eight feet tall and ripped.
我支持你
I'm with you.
我只是要确保假使我成了合成人
I just have to make sure that if I'm a synthetic human,
我也还得是犹太人
I'd still be jewish.
我答应过我妈妈
I promised my mother.
我猜你还得给你那机器人鸡鸡做个包皮手术
I suppose you could have your android penis circumcised,
但那是你的犹太教主
But that's something
和机器人制造者需要讨论的问题
Your rabbi would have to discuss with the manufacturer.
更不用说每到周六  你还得把电源关了
Not to mention you'd have to power down on saturdays.
谢尔顿  这信怎么在垃圾桶里?
Sheldon, why is this letter in the trash?
在一封信旁边自动生成一只垃圾桶
Well, there's always the possibility that a trash can
是有可能出现的事情
Spontaneously formed around the letter,
但奥卡姆剃刀定律
But occam's razor
会认为是有人把它给扔了
Would suggest that someone threw it out.
是实验物理研究院寄来的
It's from the institute for experimental physics.
他们希望我们能在
They want us to present our paper
主题为玻色-爱因斯坦凝聚的会议上
On the properties of supersolids
做我们超固体性质的论文演讲
At the topical conference on bose einstein condensates.
我知道  我扔之前看过
I know, I read it before I threw it out.
容许我把问题阐述地更清楚些
Okay, if I may drill down to the bedrock of my question
你为什么要扔了它呢
Why did you throw it out?
因为我没兴趣站在万豪国际酒店的
Because I have no interest in standing in the rose room
玫瑰间里
Of the Pasadena Marriott
去面对一群互相不认识但又喜欢评头论足的人
In front of a group of judgmental strangers
他们不会意识到
Who wouldn't recognize true genius
在他们面前做演讲的人是真正的天才
If it was standing in front of them giving a speech.
因为如果我在那  我会这么认为的
Which, if I were there, it would be.
我不知道  谢尔顿
I don't know, sheldon.
那些主题为玻色-爱因斯坦凝聚的会议
Those topical conference on bose einstein condensates
之后的庆功会都是超赞的
Parties are legendary.
别提那些庆功会
Forget the parties.
别提那些庆功会?  你个白痴
Forget the parties? what a nerd.
还有什么别的荣誉我不知道的吗
Are there any other honors I've gotten that I don't know about?
UPS有没有快递过
Did ups drop off a nobel prize
给我的诺贝尔奖?
With my name on it?
里奥纳德  你千万别误会
Leonard, please don't take this the wrong way,
不过你得诺贝尔奖的那天
But the day you win a nobel prize
就是我开始研究
Is the day I begin my research
阿拉伯飞毯上那些穗状雄花图案的风阻系数的那天
On the drag coefficient of tassels on flying carpets.
刚才那些侮辱中
Ooh, the only thing missing
唯一没有提到的就是"你妈妈"
From that insult was "your mama."
我补充一个
I got one.
里奥纳德  你妈妈的研究方法问题实在太多...
Hey, leonard, your mama's research methodology is so flawed...
闭嘴  霍华德
Shut up, howard.
谢尔顿  我们得去参加这个
Sheldon, we have to do this.
不  我们不
No, we don't.
我们得吸取营养  排除毒素
We have to take in nourishment, expel waste,
并且吸入足够的氧气来维持我们细胞鲜活
And inhale enough oxygen to keep our cells from dying.
其它任何事都不是必须的
Everything else is optional.
好  那我这么说吧  我要去参加
Okay, let me put it this way, I'm doing it.
你不能  我是第一作者
You can't. I'm the lead author.
别逗了  之所以你是第一作者
Come on, the only reason you're the lead author
是因为这是按名字字母排序的
Is because we went alphabetically.
是我让你这么认为的
I let you think we went alphabetically
好让你不用面对这一耻辱性的事实
To spare you the humiliation
那就是这篇论文是我想出来的
Of dealing with the fact that it was my idea.
不是我有意要说得那么直白
Not to put too fine a point on it,
但事实是  我在可怜你
But I was throwing you a bone.
不用谢
You're welcome.
慢着  这个假说的实验证明是我设计的
Excuse me, I designed the experiment that proved the hypothesis.
它根本就不用证明
It doesn't need proving.
这么说  整个学术界就会那么
So the entire scientific community
不加任何质疑地相信你的话?
Is just supposed to take your word?
不是会  是他们应该那样
They're not supposed to, but they should.
算了  我不管你说什么
All right, I don't care what you say,
我要去参加会议并展示我们的成果
I'm going to the conference and I'm presenting our findings.
我不允许
And I forbid it.
你不允许?
You forbid it?
如果我没有因为我们的成果而得到好评  那没人可以
If I'm not taking credit for our work, then nobody is.
-这么说你承认这是我们俩的成果?  -没有
So you admit that it's our work? no.
再说一遍  我是在可怜你
Once again, I'm throwing you a bone.
并且再说一遍  不用谢
And once again you are welcome.
不  他不会吧(模仿里奥纳德)
Oh, no, he didn't
你和谢尔顿现在怎样了
So, how's it going with sheldon?
你们还是谁也不理谁吗
Are you guys still not talking to each other?
他不但还是不跟我说话
Not only is he still not talking to me,
还会这么瞪着你  并做这么个动作
But there's this thing he does where he stares at you
试图把你的脑子弄爆
And tries to get your brain to explode.
就像那种经典的高科技电影里的扫描器
You know, like in the classic sci-fi movie scanners.
这样...
Like... bzzz...
不说了
Never mind.
这件怎么样?
How about this one?
可以告诉别人说  我是物理学家  但我也是个有趣的人
It says, I know my physics, but I'm still a fun guy.
我不知道现在还有做灯芯绒外套
Wow, I didn't know they still made corduroy suits.
是不做了  所以我才一直留着它
They don't.That's why I saved this one.
好吧  让我再看看
Okay, well, let's just see
你还有什么别的
What else you have.
拿着这个...
Okay, here, take this...
和这个  这个  还有这些...
And this, and this, and these...
所有这些你都要让我试穿?
Is this all stuff you want me to try on?
不  这些是我想让你扔了的
No, this is stuff I want you to throw out.
说真的  甚至不要把它们捐作慈善
Oh. seriously, don't even give them to charity.
你这不是在帮助任何人
You won't be helping anyone.
这是什么?
What's this?
这是坎多(对抗魔人的守卫国度)的瓶中城
That's the bottle city of kandor.
知道吗  坎多曾经是
You see, kandor was the capital city
克里顿星球(还是星球大战)的首都
Of the planet krypton.
它被天才在克里顿爆炸前缩小了
It was miniaturized by brainiac before krypton exploded,
然后被超人拯救了
And then rescued by superman.
不错
Oh. nice.
还是女孩子不看这些的时候比较好
It's a lot cooler when girls aren't looking at it.
你穿上这个试试
Here, why don't you put these on
我再看看有没有合适的T恤和运动外衣
While I find a shirt and a sport coat that match.
好  我马上回来
Great, I'll be right back.
你去哪里?  就这样换了
Where are you going? just put 'em on.
在这?
Here?
你还害羞啊?
Oh, are you shy?
没  我没害羞
No, I'm not shy.
别担心  我不会看的
Don't worry. I won't look.
我知道你不会看  你为什么要看
I know you won't look. why would you look?
这也没什么好看的...倒也不是...
There's nothing to see... well, not nothing...
亲爱的  把裤子穿上
Sweetie, put the pants on.
穿了穿了
Putting 'em on.
你跟谢尔顿在演讲这件事情上
So, you know, isn't there maybe some way
就没有互相妥协的余地吗
You and sheldon could compromise on this whole presentation thing?
不  没有
No, no.
科学家从不妥协
Scientists do not compromise.
我们的大脑被锻炼成就是把事实结合起来
Our minds are trained to synthesize facts
然后得出无可辩驳的结论
And come to inarguable conclusions.
更不用说  谢尔顿还是个怪胎
Not to mention, sheldon is bat-crap crazy.
这是什么?
What is this?
小心
Oh, careful.
那个是原版
That's my original series
太空堡垒卡拉狄加的飞行服
Battlestar galactica flight suit.
万圣节的时候你怎么没穿这个?
Oh, why didn't you wear it on halloween?
因为那不是制服  是件飞行服
Because it's not a costume. it's a flight suit.
好的  我继续找
Okay, all right, moving on.
羊毛针织花衬衫
Oh, wow, a paisley shirt.
它正好配我那件灯芯绒外套
Uh-huh, it goes with my corduroy suit.
如果你是说他们得呆在一个地方  那我同意
If you mean they should end up in the same place, then I agree.
这是你唯一的领带吗
Is this your only tie?
理论上  是的
Technically, yes.
但如果你仔细看
But if you'll notice...
会发现这是两面的
It's reversible.
所以可以当两条用
So it works as two.
亲爱的  我觉得它连一条都不算
Oh sweetie, I don't even think it works as one.
这就是你所有的衣服吗
Is this all your clothes?
对  从我八年级到现在所有的
Yup. everything since the eighth grade.
八...八年级?
The... the eighth grade?
我从那时起就不再长了
My last growth spurt.
那好  我想我们还是回到这套灯芯绒外套吧
Okay, well, I guess we're back to the corduroy suit.
好的
Great. yep.
我说了不行  扔一边去
I said no. put it down.
好啊  谢尔顿
Hey, sheldon.
你好  潘妮
Hello, penny.
有什么好东西吗
Get anything good?
最近一季度的应用粒子物理学报
Just the latest copy of applied particle physics quarterly.
真奇怪  怎么你的来了我的却没到
Oh, you know, that is so weird that yours came and mine didn't.
我开玩笑呢
It was a joke.
给女服务生点小费
Yep, tip your waitresses.
我这一周都在
I'm here all week.
潘妮  为了避免你感觉更加尴尬
Penny, just to save you from further awkwardness,
如果我们两个安安静静地走上楼
Know that I'm perfectly comfortable with the two of us
我完全没有意见
Climbing the stairs in silence.
是的  我也是
Oh, yeah, okay, me, too.
嘴巴拉上  闭紧
Zip it, lock it.
放在兜里
Put it in your pocket.
你和里奥纳德
So, you and leonard.
天呐
Oh, dear god.
有点小误会  是吧
A little misunderstanding, huh?
有点小误...?
A little misundersta...?
伽利略和教皇之间是有点小误会
Galileo and the pope had a little misunderstanding.
不管怎样  我今天早上跟里奥纳德聊天
Anyway, I was talking to leonard this morning,
我认为他对于这事感到很难过
And I think he feels really bad about it.
你是什么感受
Well, how do you feel?
你没理解你这个问题
I don't understand the question.
不  我是问和最好的朋友发生争执
No, I'm just asking if it's difficult
是不是感觉很难受
To be fighting with your best friend.
我还没那么想过
Oh, I hadn't thought about it like that.
我在想我是否正在经受
I wonder if I've been experiencing
由于无意识感情上混乱
Physiological manifestations
而导致的一些生理表现
of some sort of unconscious emotional turmoil.
等等  什么?
Wait. what?
我今天早上拉不出屎
I couldn't poop this morning.
跟他说说话吧
Just talk to him.
我想你们一定能把问题解决的
I'm sure you guys can work this out.
这肯定比我的计划更好
It's certainly preferable to my plan.
你什么计划?
Which was?
用强力泻药
A powerful laxative.
好吧  你真的应该跟他好好谈谈
Okay, so you absolutely should talk to him.
我知道里奥纳德把你当朋友的
Look, I know leonard values you as a friend,
他亲口告诉我  如果没有你那些小点子
And he told me himself that without your little idea,
他就不可能
There's no way he could have
完成这整个实验
Come up with this whole experiment thing.
不好意思  "小点子"?
Excuse me. "little idea"?
我是说  他试着跟我解释过
Yeah, I mean, he tried to explain it to me.
我没有弄得很明白...
I didn't really understand it...
你当然没明白
Of course, you didn't.
他说"小点子"?
He said, "little idea"?
不  他不是那么说的
Well, no, not in... not in those words.
那是怎么说的  确切点
In what words then, exactly?
天  确切的词是...
Um, you know, gee, the exact words...
他主要的意思是说...
It's more the spirit in which...
他说什么?
What did he say?
你只是碰运气预感到的
You had a lucky hunch.
谢尔顿  我刚才一直在想
Hey, sheldon, I've been thinking.
我们一直争执这个问题还不如...
Instead of arguing about this...
不要再跟我说话
Don't you ever speak to me again.
什...?
Wha...?
他...
He...
我去参加会议了
Okay, I'm leaving for the conference.
祝你演讲我那"幸运的预感"愉快
Have fun presenting my "lucky hunch."
谢尔顿  我不是那个意思
Shel, I didn't mean it like that.
那你为什么要那么说
Then why did you say it?
我不知道  我不是...
I don't know. I wasn't...
你是想取悦潘妮?
Were you trying to impress penny?
不  不  完全不是  有那么一点
No, no, not at all. a little bit.
那么做有效果吗
How'd that work out for you?
里奥纳德  准备走了吗
Leonard, ready to go?
力比多(弗洛伊德理论)  1-0
libido 1.0.
好  我再问你一次
Okay, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
这个成果是咱们一起完成的
We did the work together.
就让咱们一起去做演讲
Let's present the paper together.
我也跟你说最后一遍
And I'm telling you for the last time
你这是在拉皮条  这是没有尊严的  咬我吧
It's pandering, it's undignified, and bite me.
我们走吧
Let's go.
再见  谢尔顿
Bye, sheldon.
再见  潘妮
Good-bye, penny.
就在未来的某一天...
One of these days...
还不错
There you go.
你说的没错  这面果然更好看
You're right. this side does look better.
不  不  我没说"更好看"
No, no, I didn't say "better."
我只是说"褪色少一些"
I said "less stained."
我刚观察了下  里面大约
i just checked the house. there's probably
有20-25个人
20-25 people in there.
开玩笑吧?
You're kidding?
-一共就这些?  -就这些?
Is that all? "all"?
对高能物理学领域来说  25人已称得上伍德斯托克(摇滚音乐节)了
In particle physics, 25 is woodstock.
这样啊  那不错
Oh, well, then good.
我没想到会有这么多人  我有点紧张
I wasn't expecting such a crowd. I'm a little nervous.
没事  讲个笑话做开场白就不紧张了
It's okay. just open with a joke. you'll be fine.
笑话  好的
Uh, joke. okay,
这个怎么样?
How about this?
有个农民
Um, okay, uh, there's this farmer,
他养了一些鸡
And he has these chickens,
但是它们不下蛋  所以他去找物理学家求救
But they won't lay any eggs, so he calls a physicist to help.
这个物理学家便做了些计算
The physicist then does some calculations,
然后说"我有个办法
And he says, "i have a solution,
不过只适用于真空环境下的球形鸡(加拿大科学家凯伊的方法)"
But it only works with spherical chickens in a vacuum."
好笑吧?
Right?
抱歉  我...我以前听过
Oh, sorry, I just... I've heard it before.
-我们进去吧  -好的
Let's roll. okay.
西服不错
Hey, nice suit.
一流的  是吧?
It's a classic, right?
我真应该把我的车开来
I really should have brought my own car.
因此我们总结如下  数据表明
So, in conclusion, the data show
当温度接近绝对零度时
That at temperatures approaching absolute zero,
转动惯量就会发生改变
The moment of inertia changes,
而固体就会变成一种超固体
And the solid becomes a supersolid which clearly appears
成为一种之前未知的物质
To be a previously unknown state of matter.
谢谢
Thank you.
请问有任何问题吗
Were there any questions?
有  那到底是什么玩意?
Yeah, what the hell was that?
还有其他问题吗
Any other questions?
我是谢尔顿·库珀博士
Dr. sheldon cooper here.
是这篇论文的第一作者
I am the lead author of this particular paper.
谢谢
Thank you.
而你  这位先生  完全跳过了一个重要部分
And you, sir, you have completely skipped over the part
当时我是在公园里散步
Where I was walking through the park,
看见小孩们在玩旋转木马
And I saw these children on a merry-go-round,
正是这才让我想起转动惯性
Which started me thinking about the moment of inertia
当温度接近绝对零度
In gases like helium
在气体里  比如氦气里的表现
At temperatures approaching absolute zero.
我没有跳过  这只是个小插曲
I didn't skip it. it's just an anecdote.
不是科学
It's not science.
原来是这样
Oh, I see.
那么苹果落在牛顿的头上
Was the apple falling on newton's head,
也仅仅是个小插曲?
Was that just an anecdote?
你不是艾萨克·牛顿
You are not isaac newton.
是  是  这倒是不错
No, no, that's true.
对我来说  不用那苹果我也会知道是地球引力
Gravity would have been apparent to me without the apple.
你能不能不那么自大
You could not possibly be that arrogant.
你仍旧低估了我  我的伙计
You continue to underestimate me, my good man.
听着  如果你因为我的演讲而不高兴
Look, if you weren't happy with my presentation,
那你应该跟我一起来讲的
Then maybe you should have given it with me.
就像我反复解释的  我不像你
As I've explained repeatedly, unlike you,
我不需要比我笨的人来认可我
I don't need validation from lesser minds.
没有别的意思
No offense.
那你还为什么来?
So why did you come?
因为我知道你会把它糟蹋了的
Because I knew you'd screw this up.
我才没有糟蹋
I didn't screw it up
开玩笑
Oh, please,
-我承认那个球形鸡的笑话...是挺好笑  -谢谢
I admit that spherical chicken joke-- that was hilarious. Thanks.
不过从那里开始就急转直下了
But it was straight downhill from there.
我受够了你这种高傲的态度
I've had enough of your condescension.
也许我没有像你一样11岁就考上大学
Maybe I didn't go to college when I was 11 like you.
也许我是24岁才拿到博士  而不像你是16岁
Maybe I got my doctorate at 24 instead of 16,
但你不是这个屋子里
But you are not the only person
唯一一个比他们都聪明的人
Who is smarter than everyone else in this room
没别的意思
No offense.
我显然并不是这里唯一一个
And I am clearly not the only person
怀着不安全感  渴望得到
Who is tormented by insecurity
不断的肯定  并为之饱受苦恼的人
And has an ego in need of constant validation.
那你承认你是个自大狂了?
So you admit that you're an egotist?
对
Yes
我是里奥纳德·霍夫斯塔德博士
My name is dr. leonard hofstadter
我从不讨我父母喜欢
And I could never please my parents,
所以我需要从你们这些陌生人这里
So I need to get all my self-esteem
把自尊心都找回来
From strangers like you.
但他更差劲
But he's worse
-好的  够了  -别闹了
Okay, that is it stop it
你不可能用意念爆了我的头
You cannot blow up my head with your mind
那给你弄个动脉瘤也成
Then I'll settle for an aneurysm.
别弄了
Stop it
你打我
You hit me
你们都看到了  他打我
You saw that. he hit me.
是你想爆了我的头
You were trying to blow up my head.
所以还是起作用了
So it was working.
才不是呢  你简直是个疯子
It was not you are a nut case
我们来看看
We'll see about that.
把头抬起来  坐第一排的人
Heads up, you people in the front row.
这里是辐射区
This is a splash zone.
别闹了
Stop it
停下来
Quit it
你们搞物理的经常这样?
Is this usually how these physics things go?
比你想的要频繁
More often than you think.
停下  我要发功把你弄爆
Stop it nerve pinch
你可以让我搭车一起回来的
You could have offered me a ride home.
我没开车把你碾过去你已经很幸运了
You're lucky I didn't run you over.
我真不知道你在不开心些什么
I really don't understand what you're so unhappy about.
你求我去  我去了
You begged me to come. I came.
结果你还是不高兴
There's just no pleasing you.
没错  问题都在我这
You're right. I'm the problem.
我是那个需要帮助的人
I'm the one that needs help.
这不是很像道歉
Well, that's not much of an apology,
但我接受了
But I'll take it.
等等
Excuse me.
你有没有什么想向我道歉?
Is there anything you would like to apologize for?
有
Yes.
我有想要爆了你的头  对不起
I'm sorry I tried to blow up your head.
那样做没有必要
It was uncalled for.
你们不会相信的
You won't believe this.
有人把整件事情经过用手机拍下来了
Somebody got the whole thing on a cell phone
并上传到了Youtube
And put it on youtube.
什么?
What?
谁会这么缺德?
Now who would do that?
是我
That would be me.
快来看看  很有意思的视频
Hey, check it out. it's a featured video.
你打我
You hit me
你们都看到了  他打我
You saw that he hit me
是你想爆了我的头
You're trying to blow up my head.
所以还是起作用了
So it was working.
别弄了  你简直是个疯子
Stop it you're a nut case.
我们来看看
We'll see about that.
你们前排的人  把头抬起来  这里是辐射区
You people in the front row, heads up. this is a splash zone.
别闹了
Stop it
停下来  停下来
Quit it quit it
我要发功把你弄爆
Put you in a vulcan nerve pinch
你应该剪剪指甲  真疼死了
Ow, you should cut your fingernails. those hurt
天  这套西服真的这么难看?
Oh, geez, does this suit really look that bad?
别提你那西服了
Forget your suit.
看我胳臂挥的
Look at my arms waving.
像是利他林(一种兴奋剂)上的那只红鹤
I'm like a flamingo on ritalin.
霍华德
Howard,
你能不能向我解释下
Would you like to explain to me
为什么你的facebook(国外交友网站)主页上有张我靠在你
Why your facebook page has a picture of me sleeping
肩膀睡觉的照片  并且标题是我和我的女友?
On your shoulder captioned "me and my girlfriend"?
又得好好解释下了
here comes the talk.
(中国某地)
somewhere in China
什么混蛋东西嘛
What losers.
对呀  很大的书呆子
Yeah. Gigantic American geeks.
谁在搞鬼?
Who's doing that?
一个来自加利福尼亚州的帕萨迪纳
Someone from Pasadena, California named...
叫"沃尔巫师"的人
"Wolowizard"
酷毙了
Awesome.